<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Hugo website</title>
    <link>https://uncaged-coder.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://uncaged-coder.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Starting a Blog with Hugo, R Markdown, and Python (Reticulate)</title>
      <link>https://uncaged-coder.github.io/2023/starting-a-blog-with-hugo-r-markdown-and-python-reticulate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uncaged-coder.github.io/2023/starting-a-blog-with-hugo-r-markdown-and-python-reticulate/</guid>
      <description>I always prioritize simplicity. While many people today blog using platforms like WordPress, complete with an array of plugins and PHP-driven dynamic content, such complexity is often unnecessary. Take a moment to consider: why do we need dynamic content for something as straightforward as a blog?
Traditional blogging platforms frequently expose users to security risks, especially when built on languages like PHP. Consequently, I’ve chosen to use a static site generator, Hugo, in conjunction with R Markdown and Python via the Reticulate package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of Ego, Fear, and Conflict: Towards a Transcendence for Conflict Resolution</title>
      <link>https://uncaged-coder.github.io/2023/of-ego-fear-and-conflict-towards-a-transcendence-for-conflict-resolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uncaged-coder.github.io/2023/of-ego-fear-and-conflict-towards-a-transcendence-for-conflict-resolution/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: The Triad of Conflict In humanity’s constant endeavor to understand the conflictual nature of our existence, we have examined various facets of our behavior and interactions. At the heart of these reflections lie three interconnected and powerful factors: the desire to impose one’s viewpoint, fear, and ego. These three elements are often present in conflicts, whether they are interpersonal, social, or international.
Dove representing peace
The desire to impose one’s viewpoint: A Breeding Ground for Conflict Let’s start with the desire to impose one’s viewpoint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://uncaged-coder.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uncaged-coder.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a &amp;ldquo;hello world&amp;rdquo; example website for the blogdown package. The theme was forked from @jrutheiser/hugo-lithium-theme and modified by Yihui Xie.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
